{
  "uniqueId": "anagrams3",
  "name": "Anagrams Length 3 Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Unscramable the below word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "RANDOMIZE_QUESTION_CHARACTERS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_ANSWER",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "STRICT",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "ace",
      "answer": "ace"
    },
    {
      "question": "act",
      "answer": "act"
    },
    {
      "question": "add",
      "answer": "add"
    },
    {
      "question": "aft",
      "answer": "aft"
    },
    {
      "question": "age",
      "answer": "age"
    },
    {
      "question": "ago",
      "answer": "ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "aha",
      "answer": "aha"
    },
    {
      "question": "aid",
      "answer": "aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "ail",
      "answer": "ail"
    },
    {
      "question": "aim",
      "answer": "aim"
    },
    {
      "question": "air",
      "answer": "air"
    },
    {
      "question": "ale",
      "answer": "ale"
    },
    {
      "question": "all",
      "answer": "all"
    },
    {
      "question": "alp",
      "answer": "alp"
    },
    {
      "question": "and",
      "answer": "and"
    },
    {
      "question": "ant",
      "answer": "ant"
    },
    {
      "question": "any",
      "answer": "any"
    },
    {
      "question": "ape",
      "answer": "ape"
    },
    {
      "question": "apt",
      "answer": "apt"
    },
    {
      "question": "arc",
      "answer": "arc"
    },
    {
      "question": "are",
      "answer": "are"
    },
    {
      "question": "ark",
      "answer": "ark"
    },
    {
      "question": "arm",
      "answer": "arm"
    },
    {
      "question": "art",
      "answer": "art"
    },
    {
      "question": "ash",
      "answer": "ash"
    },
    {
      "question": "ask",
      "answer": "ask"
    },
    {
      "question": "asp",
      "answer": "asp"
    },
    {
      "question": "ate",
      "answer": "ate"
    },
    {
      "question": "awe",
      "answer": "awe"
    },
    {
      "question": "awl",
      "answer": "awl"
    },
    {
      "question": "aye",
      "answer": "aye"
    },
    {
      "question": "bad",
      "answer": "bad"
    },
    {
      "question": "bag",
      "answer": "bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "ban",
      "answer": "ban"
    },
    {
      "question": "bar",
      "answer": "bar"
    },
    {
      "question": "bat",
      "answer": "bat"
    },
    {
      "question": "bay",
      "answer": "bay"
    },
    {
      "question": "bed",
      "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "bee",
      "answer": "bee"
    },
    {
      "question": "beg",
      "answer": "beg"
    },
    {
      "question": "bet",
      "answer": "bet"
    },
    {
      "question": "bey",
      "answer": "bey"
    },
    {
      "question": "bid",
      "answer": "bid"
    },
    {
      "question": "big",
      "answer": "big"
    },
    {
      "question": "bin",
      "answer": "bin"
    },
    {
      "question": "bit",
      "answer": "bit"
    },
    {
      "question": "bog",
      "answer": "bog"
    },
    {
      "question": "bow",
      "answer": "bow"
    },
    {
      "question": "box",
      "answer": "box"
    },
    {
      "question": "boy",
      "answer": "boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "bra",
      "answer": "bra"
    },
    {
      "question": "bud",
      "answer": "bud"
    },
    {
      "question": "bug",
      "answer": "bug"
    },
    {
      "question": "bun",
      "answer": "bun"
    },
    {
      "question": "bur",
      "answer": "bur"
    },
    {
      "question": "bus",
      "answer": "bus"
    },
    {
      "question": "but",
      "answer": "but"
    },
    {
      "question": "buy",
      "answer": "buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "bye",
      "answer": "bye"
    },
    {
      "question": "cab",
      "answer": "cab"
    },
    {
      "question": "can",
      "answer": "can"
    },
    {
      "question": "cap",
      "answer": "cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "car",
      "answer": "car"
    },
    {
      "question": "cat",
      "answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "cod",
      "answer": "cod"
    },
    {
      "question": "cop",
      "answer": "cop"
    },
    {
      "question": "cot",
      "answer": "cot"
    },
    {
      "question": "cow",
      "answer": "cow"
    },
    {
      "question": "coy",
      "answer": "coy"
    },
    {
      "question": "cry",
      "answer": "cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "cub",
      "answer": "cub"
    },
    {
      "question": "cue",
      "answer": "cue"
    },
    {
      "question": "cup",
      "answer": "cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut",
      "answer": "cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "dab",
      "answer": "dab"
    },
    {
      "question": "dad",
      "answer": "dad"
    },
    {
      "question": "dam",
      "answer": "dam"
    },
    {
      "question": "day",
      "answer": "day"
    },
    {
      "question": "deb",
      "answer": "deb"
    },
    {
      "question": "den",
      "answer": "den"
    },
    {
      "question": "dew",
      "answer": "dew"
    },
    {
      "question": "did",
      "answer": "did"
    },
    {
      "question": "die",
      "answer": "die"
    },
    {
      "question": "dig",
      "answer": "dig"
    },
    {
      "question": "dim",
      "answer": "dim"
    },
    {
      "question": "din",
      "answer": "din"
    },
    {
      "question": "dip",
      "answer": "dip"
    },
    {
      "question": "doe",
      "answer": "doe"
    },
    {
      "question": "dog",
      "answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "don",
      "answer": "don"
    },
    {
      "question": "dot",
      "answer": "dot"
    },
    {
      "question": "dry",
      "answer": "dry"
    },
    {
      "question": "dub",
      "answer": "dub"
    },
    {
      "question": "due",
      "answer": "due"
    },
    {
      "question": "duo",
      "answer": "duo"
    },
    {
      "question": "dye",
      "answer": "dye"
    },
    {
      "question": "ear",
      "answer": "ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "eat",
      "answer": "eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "ebb",
      "answer": "ebb"
    },
    {
      "question": "egg",
      "answer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "ego",
      "answer": "ego"
    },
    {
      "question": "elf",
      "answer": "elf"
    },
    {
      "question": "end",
      "answer": "end"
    },
    {
      "question": "eon",
      "answer": "eon"
    },
    {
      "question": "era",
      "answer": "era"
    },
    {
      "question": "err",
      "answer": "err"
    },
    {
      "question": "eve",
      "answer": "eve"
    },
    {
      "question": "ewe",
      "answer": "ewe"
    },
    {
      "question": "eye",
      "answer": "eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "fan",
      "answer": "fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "far",
      "answer": "far"
    },
    {
      "question": "fat",
      "answer": "fat"
    },
    {
      "question": "fax",
      "answer": "fax"
    },
    {
      "question": "fee",
      "answer": "fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "few",
      "answer": "few"
    },
    {
      "question": "fig",
      "answer": "fig"
    },
    {
      "question": "fin",
      "answer": "fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "fir",
      "answer": "fir"
    },
    {
      "question": "fit",
      "answer": "fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "fix",
      "answer": "fix"
    },
    {
      "question": "flu",
      "answer": "flu"
    },
    {
      "question": "fly",
      "answer": "fly"
    },
    {
      "question": "foe",
      "answer": "foe"
    },
    {
      "question": "fog",
      "answer": "fog"
    },
    {
      "question": "for",
      "answer": "for"
    },
    {
      "question": "fox",
      "answer": "fox"
    },
    {
      "question": "fro",
      "answer": "fro"
    },
    {
      "question": "fry",
      "answer": "fry"
    },
    {
      "question": "fun",
      "answer": "fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "fur",
      "answer": "fur"
    },
    {
      "question": "gab",
      "answer": "gab"
    },
    {
      "question": "gag",
      "answer": "gag"
    },
    {
      "question": "gap",
      "answer": "gap"
    },
    {
      "question": "gas",
      "answer": "gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "gay",
      "answer": "gay"
    },
    {
      "question": "gee",
      "answer": "gee"
    },
    {
      "question": "gem",
      "answer": "gem"
    },
    {
      "question": "get",
      "answer": "get"
    },
    {
      "question": "gig",
      "answer": "gig"
    },
    {
      "question": "gin",
      "answer": "gin"
    },
    {
      "question": "gnu",
      "answer": "gnu"
    },
    {
      "question": "gob",
      "answer": "gob"
    },
    {
      "question": "god",
      "answer": "god"
    },
    {
      "question": "gum",
      "answer": "gum"
    },
    {
      "question": "gun",
      "answer": "gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "guy",
      "answer": "guy"
    },
    {
      "question": "gym",
      "answer": "gym"
    },
    {
      "question": "ham",
      "answer": "ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "has",
      "answer": "has"
    },
    {
      "question": "hat",
      "answer": "hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "hay",
      "answer": "hay"
    },
    {
      "question": "hem",
      "answer": "hem"
    },
    {
      "question": "hen",
      "answer": "hen"
    },
    {
      "question": "her",
      "answer": "her"
    },
    {
      "question": "hey",
      "answer": "hey"
    },
    {
      "question": "him",
      "answer": "him"
    },
    {
      "question": "hip",
      "answer": "hip"
    },
    {
      "question": "his",
      "answer": "his"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit",
      "answer": "hit"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoe",
      "answer": "hoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "hog",
      "answer": "hog"
    },
    {
      "question": "hop",
      "answer": "hop"
    },
    {
      "question": "hot",
      "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "how",
      "answer": "how"
    },
    {
      "question": "hub",
      "answer": "hub"
    },
    {
      "question": "hue",
      "answer": "hue"
    },
    {
      "question": "hug",
      "answer": "hug"
    },
    {
      "question": "hum",
      "answer": "hum"
    },
    {
      "question": "hut",
      "answer": "hut"
    },
    {
      "question": "ice",
      "answer": "ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "icy",
      "answer": "icy"
    },
    {
      "question": "ill",
      "answer": "ill"
    },
    {
      "question": "ink",
      "answer": "ink"
    },
    {
      "question": "inn",
      "answer": "inn"
    },
    {
      "question": "ion",
      "answer": "ion"
    },
    {
      "question": "its",
      "answer": "its"
    },
    {
      "question": "jab",
      "answer": "jab"
    },
    {
      "question": "jam",
      "answer": "jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "jar",
      "answer": "jar"
    },
    {
      "question": "jaw",
      "answer": "jaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "jay",
      "answer": "jay"
    },
    {
      "question": "jet",
      "answer": "jet"
    },
    {
      "question": "job",
      "answer": "job"
    },
    {
      "question": "jog",
      "answer": "jog"
    },
    {
      "question": "jot",
      "answer": "jot"
    },
    {
      "question": "joy",
      "answer": "joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "jug",
      "answer": "jug"
    },
    {
      "question": "jut",
      "answer": "jut"
    },
    {
      "question": "key",
      "answer": "key"
    },
    {
      "question": "kid",
      "answer": "kid"
    },
    {
      "question": "kin",
      "answer": "kin"
    },
    {
      "question": "kit",
      "answer": "kit"
    },
    {
      "question": "lad",
      "answer": "lad"
    },
    {
      "question": "lag",
      "answer": "lag"
    },
    {
      "question": "lap",
      "answer": "lap"
    },
    {
      "question": "law",
      "answer": "law"
    },
    {
      "question": "lax",
      "answer": "lax"
    },
    {
      "question": "lay",
      "answer": "lay"
    },
    {
      "question": "lea",
      "answer": "lea"
    },
    {
      "question": "leg",
      "answer": "leg"
    },
    {
      "question": "lei",
      "answer": "lei"
    },
    {
      "question": "let",
      "answer": "let"
    },
    {
      "question": "lid",
      "answer": "lid"
    },
    {
      "question": "lie",
      "answer": "lie"
    },
    {
      "question": "lip",
      "answer": "lip"
    },
    {
      "question": "lob",
      "answer": "lob"
    },
    {
      "question": "log",
      "answer": "log"
    },
    {
      "question": "lot",
      "answer": "lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "low",
      "answer": "low"
    },
    {
      "question": "mad",
      "answer": "mad"
    },
    {
      "question": "man",
      "answer": "man"
    },
    {
      "question": "map",
      "answer": "map"
    },
    {
      "question": "mar",
      "answer": "mar"
    },
    {
      "question": "mat",
      "answer": "mat"
    },
    {
      "question": "may",
      "answer": "may"
    },
    {
      "question": "men",
      "answer": "men"
    },
    {
      "question": "mid",
      "answer": "mid"
    },
    {
      "question": "mix",
      "answer": "mix"
    },
    {
      "question": "mud",
      "answer": "mud"
    },
    {
      "question": "mug",
      "answer": "mug"
    },
    {
      "question": "nab",
      "answer": "nab"
    },
    {
      "question": "nag",
      "answer": "nag"
    },
    {
      "question": "nap",
      "answer": "nap"
    },
    {
      "question": "nay",
      "answer": "nay"
    },
    {
      "question": "net",
      "answer": "net"
    },
    {
      "question": "new",
      "answer": "new"
    },
    {
      "question": "nib",
      "answer": "nib"
    },
    {
      "question": "nil",
      "answer": "nil"
    },
    {
      "question": "nip",
      "answer": "nip"
    },
    {
      "question": "nit",
      "answer": "nit"
    },
    {
      "question": "nod",
      "answer": "nod"
    },
    {
      "question": "nor",
      "answer": "nor"
    },
    {
      "question": "not",
      "answer": "not"
    },
    {
      "question": "now",
      "answer": "now"
    },
    {
      "question": "nub",
      "answer": "nub"
    },
    {
      "question": "nun",
      "answer": "nun"
    },
    {
      "question": "nut",
      "answer": "nut"
    },
    {
      "question": "oak",
      "answer": "oak"
    },
    {
      "question": "oar",
      "answer": "oar"
    },
    {
      "question": "oat",
      "answer": "oat"
    },
    {
      "question": "odd",
      "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
      "question": "ode",
      "answer": "ode"
    },
    {
      "question": "off",
      "answer": "off"
    },
    {
      "question": "oil",
      "answer": "oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "old",
      "answer": "old"
    },
    {
      "question": "one",
      "answer": "one"
    },
    {
      "question": "opt",
      "answer": "opt"
    },
    {
      "question": "orb",
      "answer": "orb"
    },
    {
      "question": "ore",
      "answer": "ore"
    },
    {
      "question": "our",
      "answer": "our"
    },
    {
      "question": "out",
      "answer": "out"
    },
    {
      "question": "owe",
      "answer": "owe"
    },
    {
      "question": "owl",
      "answer": "owl"
    },
    {
      "question": "own",
      "answer": "own"
    },
    {
      "question": "pad",
      "answer": "pad"
    },
    {
      "question": "pal",
      "answer": "pal"
    },
    {
      "question": "pan",
      "answer": "pan"
    },
    {
      "question": "pas",
      "answer": "pas"
    },
    {
      "question": "pat",
      "answer": "pat"
    },
    {
      "question": "paw",
      "answer": "paw"
    },
    {
      "question": "pay",
      "answer": "pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "pea",
      "answer": "pea"
    },
    {
      "question": "peg",
      "answer": "peg"
    },
    {
      "question": "pen",
      "answer": "pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "pep",
      "answer": "pep"
    },
    {
      "question": "per",
      "answer": "per"
    },
    {
      "question": "pet",
      "answer": "pet"
    },
    {
      "question": "pew",
      "answer": "pew"
    },
    {
      "question": "pie",
      "answer": "pie"
    },
    {
      "question": "pig",
      "answer": "pig"
    },
    {
      "question": "pin",
      "answer": "pin"
    },
    {
      "question": "pit",
      "answer": "pit"
    },
    {
      "question": "ply",
      "answer": "ply"
    },
    {
      "question": "pod",
      "answer": "pod"
    },
    {
      "question": "pop",
      "answer": "pop"
    },
    {
      "question": "pot",
      "answer": "pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "pry",
      "answer": "pry"
    },
    {
      "question": "pub",
      "answer": "pub"
    },
    {
      "question": "pun",
      "answer": "pun"
    },
    {
      "question": "put",
      "answer": "put"
    },
    {
      "question": "pya",
      "answer": "pya"
    },
    {
      "question": "rag",
      "answer": "rag"
    },
    {
      "question": "ram",
      "answer": "ram"
    },
    {
      "question": "rat",
      "answer": "rat"
    },
    {
      "question": "raw",
      "answer": "raw"
    },
    {
      "question": "ray",
      "answer": "ray"
    },
    {
      "question": "red",
      "answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "question": "rib",
      "answer": "rib"
    },
    {
      "question": "rid",
      "answer": "rid"
    },
    {
      "question": "rig",
      "answer": "rig"
    },
    {
      "question": "rim",
      "answer": "rim"
    },
    {
      "question": "rip",
      "answer": "rip"
    },
    {
      "question": "rob",
      "answer": "rob"
    },
    {
      "question": "rod",
      "answer": "rod"
    },
    {
      "question": "roe",
      "answer": "roe"
    },
    {
      "question": "rot",
      "answer": "rot"
    },
    {
      "question": "row",
      "answer": "row"
    },
    {
      "question": "rub",
      "answer": "rub"
    },
    {
      "question": "rue",
      "answer": "rue"
    },
    {
      "question": "rug",
      "answer": "rug"
    },
    {
      "question": "run",
      "answer": "run"
    },
    {
      "question": "rut",
      "answer": "rut"
    },
    {
      "question": "sad",
      "answer": "sad"
    },
    {
      "question": "sag",
      "answer": "sag"
    },
    {
      "question": "sap",
      "answer": "sap"
    },
    {
      "question": "saw",
      "answer": "saw"
    },
    {
      "question": "say",
      "answer": "say"
    },
    {
      "question": "sea",
      "answer": "sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "see",
      "answer": "see"
    },
    {
      "question": "set",
      "answer": "set"
    },
    {
      "question": "sew",
      "answer": "sew"
    },
    {
      "question": "she",
      "answer": "she"
    },
    {
      "question": "shy",
      "answer": "shy"
    },
    {
      "question": "sin",
      "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
      "question": "sip",
      "answer": "sip"
    },
    {
      "question": "sir",
      "answer": "sir"
    },
    {
      "question": "sit",
      "answer": "sit"
    },
    {
      "question": "six",
      "answer": "six"
    },
    {
      "question": "ski",
      "answer": "ski"
    },
    {
      "question": "sky",
      "answer": "sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "sly",
      "answer": "sly"
    },
    {
      "question": "sob",
      "answer": "sob"
    },
    {
      "question": "sod",
      "answer": "sod"
    },
    {
      "question": "son",
      "answer": "son"
    },
    {
      "question": "sow",
      "answer": "sow"
    },
    {
      "question": "spa",
      "answer": "spa"
    },
    {
      "question": "spy",
      "answer": "spy"
    },
    {
      "question": "sub",
      "answer": "sub"
    },
    {
      "question": "sue",
      "answer": "sue"
    },
    {
      "question": "sum",
      "answer": "sum"
    },
    {
      "question": "sun",
      "answer": "sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "tab",
      "answer": "tab"
    },
    {
      "question": "tag",
      "answer": "tag"
    },
    {
      "question": "tam",
      "answer": "tam"
    },
    {
      "question": "tan",
      "answer": "tan"
    },
    {
      "question": "tap",
      "answer": "tap"
    },
    {
      "question": "tar",
      "answer": "tar"
    },
    {
      "question": "tax",
      "answer": "tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "tea",
      "answer": "tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "tee",
      "answer": "tee"
    },
    {
      "question": "ten",
      "answer": "ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "the",
      "answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "question": "tie",
      "answer": "tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "tin",
      "answer": "tin"
    },
    {
      "question": "tip",
      "answer": "tip"
    },
    {
      "question": "toe",
      "answer": "toe"
    },
    {
      "question": "ton",
      "answer": "ton"
    },
    {
      "question": "too",
      "answer": "too"
    },
    {
      "question": "top",
      "answer": "top"
    },
    {
      "question": "tor",
      "answer": "tor"
    },
    {
      "question": "tow",
      "answer": "tow"
    },
    {
      "question": "toy",
      "answer": "toy"
    },
    {
      "question": "try",
      "answer": "try"
    },
    {
      "question": "tub",
      "answer": "tub"
    },
    {
      "question": "tun",
      "answer": "tun"
    },
    {
      "question": "two",
      "answer": "two"
    },
    {
      "question": "urn",
      "answer": "urn"
    },
    {
      "question": "use",
      "answer": "use"
    },
    {
      "question": "van",
      "answer": "van"
    },
    {
      "question": "vat",
      "answer": "vat"
    },
    {
      "question": "vex",
      "answer": "vex"
    },
    {
      "question": "via",
      "answer": "via"
    },
    {
      "question": "vie",
      "answer": "vie"
    },
    {
      "question": "vow",
      "answer": "vow"
    },
    {
      "question": "war",
      "answer": "war"
    },
    {
      "question": "was",
      "answer": "was"
    },
    {
      "question": "wax",
      "answer": "wax"
    },
    {
      "question": "way",
      "answer": "way"
    },
    {
      "question": "web",
      "answer": "web"
    },
    {
      "question": "wed",
      "answer": "wed"
    },
    {
      "question": "wee",
      "answer": "wee"
    },
    {
      "question": "wen",
      "answer": "wen"
    },
    {
      "question": "wet",
      "answer": "wet"
    },
    {
      "question": "who",
      "answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "question": "why",
      "answer": "why"
    },
    {
      "question": "wig",
      "answer": "wig"
    },
    {
      "question": "win",
      "answer": "win"
    },
    {
      "question": "wit",
      "answer": "wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "woe",
      "answer": "woe"
    },
    {
      "question": "won",
      "answer": "won"
    },
    {
      "question": "woo",
      "answer": "woo"
    },
    {
      "question": "wry",
      "answer": "wry"
    },
    {
      "question": "yam",
      "answer": "yam"
    },
    {
      "question": "yap",
      "answer": "yap"
    },
    {
      "question": "yaw",
      "answer": "yaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "yea",
      "answer": "yea"
    },
    {
      "question": "yes",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "yet",
      "answer": "yet"
    },
    {
      "question": "you",
      "answer": "you"
    },
    {
      "question": "zip",
      "answer": "zip"
    },
    {
      "question": "zoo",
      "answer": "zoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "mom",
      "answer": "mom"
    },
    {
      "question": "lab",
      "answer": "lab"
    },
    {
      "question": "etc",
      "answer": "etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "wow",
      "answer": "wow"
    },
    {
      "question": "huh",
      "answer": "huh"
    },
    {
      "question": "pro",
      "answer": "pro"
    },
    {
      "question": "gut",
      "answer": "gut"
    }
  ]
}